(Amy:)Try and get that nag
off your back, right?
I mean, you're not a bicycle;
(Amy:)why's she riding you like that?
(Penny:)No, I think she was
just trying to help.
(Penny:)Plus, I really want to do well
at this job. So...
(Amy:)Okay, good luck.
And call me later,
(Amy:)you know, if you decide
she's a bitch or something.
(Amy(on phone):)Hey, girlfriend.
(Bernadette:)Hey, Amy.
(Amy:)Tonight. You, me, Color Me Mine.
(Amy:)Maybe we sneak in some pinot--
make it Color Me Wine.
(Bernadette:)That sounds fun,
but I promised Penny
(Bernadette:)I'd come by and help her study.
(Amy:)Oh. Well, good luck
getting her to do that.
(Amy:)She's probably off
getting another manicure.
(Amy:)You remember when she did that?
(Amy:)You remember?
(Bernadette:)I was probably being
too hard on her.
(Bernadette:)We talked, we're good.
(Amy:)Oh. Great.
(Amy:)I'm happy for you guys.
(Amy:)You know, when the two of you
aren't getting along,
(Amy:)it puts me in a really
weird position.
(Bernadette:)Well, don't worry--
everything's back to normal.
(Amy:)You mean, like, where she's nice
to your face? Okay got it. Bye.